Hello
[music] Wait
a minute, Mr.
Mituhal, hello, nice to meet you.
Oh, this is because I just sat down at the right time, but the
microphone
[music] has
one of its legs missing from the microphone stand.
But it's supposed to be tightened with a bolt and nut, but I
don't know where the nut is. There's a
bolt, but I can't see the nut.
Because of the leg, one of the legs is missing, so the
microphone can't be used,
so I'm propping it up with something else on the side for
now. Because of this, it's hard to use the keyboard right now, and I
think I need to arrange it better.
Nice to meet
you, Mr. Amores, hello,
thank you.
I'll start by showing you some of my pictures. The
microphone is bothering me.
These days, I only make money through video, so
tomorrow will be the
same.
In the big picture,
it's raining again today,
but the rain has passed,
so the cows
are living in a cleaner environment. The
water hasn't spread yet, so it
's still muddy. Every
time they step on it, they dig in.
So when the sun shines too hard, it's
hot, so the
kids try to stay in the shade inside the next car,
and
the inside of the car where there's shade is completely
muddy again.  It was so bad because it was so hot.
But
it hasn't rained right away lately, but it's been
cloudy and blocking the sun,
so the weather is
n't that hot anymore. And because it's not that hot anymore,
the kids do
n't necessarily stay inside reading books anymore. They come out and play
hard and use the space more widely, so it's a
little cleaner and nicer. The
heat is a problem, and the rain
is also a problem. The
rainy season is ending soon, so it's going to
be incredibly hot again. And a
typhoon is coming. It's
not like everything will be solved just because one thing is over.
Hello, Harling.
Oh, and it seems like it's because the weather's gotten warmer,
but the Muscovites have
n't laid horses. They
laid five, six, and today they laid six.
Five the day before yesterday, six yesterday, and six today. It seems like Muscovites won't be able to turn a profit this year. When I brought them here, they laid two or three for two months,
but now they're starting
to come out at a dozen or so. I thought they'd finally start to turn around little by little, but they're
12,000 won a day, and
I thought it would increase.
Now they're  Since there are 49 of them, I
thought they would produce around 30 if they continued to increase at this rate, but
that's not the case. They
decreased again and only five or six were produced. It's
heartbreaking.
Oh, and there's another interesting photo.
I don't remember if I made it into a video when I was broadcasting before, but I've
shown it before.
Grasses
put down roots deeper than you think. Not all grasses are like
that.
Four-year-old grasses are like that. When
we
look at a huge forest, we see the enormous trees in that forest, the
trunks of those trees, the
enormous branches that just extend upwards, and the
huge shade they create, and we
feel awe
and think, "Wow, that's amazing." But actually,
when we look at grasses, we do
n't really know that. If they
root, they're
not just weeds. We think about it this way.
Grasses also put down roots this deep and
when they grow well in the right environment,
they actually
hold onto the soil better and
play a role in that. They
capture much more carbon than forests with trees at a faster rate than organic matter in forests.
And you
can isolate them on the ground and do that.
Their life cycle is much faster,
so
hello.
[Music]
Oh, and
there was another accident.
Oh, last
night, I was coming back after dinner, and
on that day, I
was coming down from the field like this from the mountain, and it's a bit
mountainous, so I had to come down from there. After
coming down, I had to take it back to the main road, but as I was coming,
all of a sudden,
a bunch of piglets
came rushing out. They just poured down onto the road,
like water had been spilled.
Of course, I've seen them on videos and
stuff, but
that
was the first time I'd seen them alive. All of a sudden, all of the
piglets just
poured out and
ran onto the road. There
were about six or seven of them. Oh,
so I was startled and
things like that happened quite a bit. Before that,
when Mr. Thailand was there, if there
was a roe deer in front of us, we were going to
hit it and we were discussing whether or not we should eat
it.
And that too. Now,
if you avoid animals for no reason, people get hurt, so to
a certain extent, just don't push yourself too hard and if it
seems like it won't work, hit it.  I was
a little worried about whether to kill them or not, but I
dodged a little because the water was pouring down.
But since the road was good, my car's
tire hit the cement curb next to it. It made a
thud,
and the boars just continued down like this. Then, I was like, "What the heck?" and I was about to
turn the car around and go back, but the
steering wheel was weird. The
car felt weird and the sound
was weird. Didn't the
tire blow out again?
Didn't they talk about it on the broadcast a while ago when it blew out outside? Anyway, it was raining that
day, and I think the tire hit a
rock or something. It
blew out, and I was
discharged from the garage at the time, and it was night. It was
past 8:30.
Anyway, I had to get the tire
fixed so I could go home. Since it was
in front of the insurance company, it
took about 50 minutes for them to come to the field, and they were
coming from downtown Gimcheon, so it took the same amount of
time for me to get to the field from my house.
Even then, it took 50 minutes to get there,
fix it, and go back. I
put on a spare tire and drove around a few times.
So, not long after that, the
tire problem is happening again.  I
thought I'd lost it, so I asked, "Miss, what's this?" and
got out to look again.
The tire wasn't punctured. It was
n't punctured, but it
seemed to be crooked. I turned the steering wheel like this and rammed it, and as I turned it, it somehow caught on the curb like this, and the wheel seemed to be slightly crooked.
So, if I were to compare it to a person, it would be like
this: the tires should be straight,
but this one is normal, but this one is crooked. If it were to
continue like this, the car would go in
one direction. So, I turned the steering wheel slightly so that the tires were crooked and slightly in the middle. So, instead of rolling like this, the tires would start to drift a little, like in the old Christopher Nolan Batman series, where Batman's car would roll sideways. The
car wheels would
start to roll sideways a little.
So, when I drove
straight, it would make a
drifting sound. The
steering wheel would shake a lot, and
something kept happening. The wheel was
in that state. I somehow managed to get home,
but I
couldn't go to the tire shop the next morning. I had to
go straight to the garage, but
I woke up and just
went there and came back.
So now  I drove 10km in that condition
and then
this morning, after
finishing all the work, organizing, and sorting things out, I
went to the tire shop again. It's
been a while since I've been here, so I went again, but this itself,
and all of my child's tires, were old. I
had a new pair of
tires in February. Back then, the tires had blown out. At that time,
I had just received tires that my grandfather had been using, and they
had naturally worn out and
started leaking air.
So I replaced all four tires with new ones.
But not long after, I tripped on a rock on a rainy day and
blew a tire. That's when I replaced them with used tires. Then, while
avoiding a wild
boar, I thought, "At first, I just
needed to balance it. The
steering wheel
was a little off, so I
just needed to straighten this wheel like this." But since I was already driving with about 120kg, the tires were completely destroyed. This side didn't touch at all, but
this side was off, so the
car rolled strangely in that direction.
So one side was completely
off, and the other side was too.  They said that they were strangely
attached and that both had to be replaced.
No, actually, I thought this one was
definitely removable. I
thought I only needed to replace one, but the other side was also
attached,
so I went
back today and replaced the tire.
No, what kind of
tire
was that?
And I've been uploading the rest of
the news
as stories on Instagram.
This is
my Instagram. If you look here,
there are highlights. If you
look at "Free Grazing" and "2023 Park Mok-seo-so," I've
uploaded everything I've been up to. I haven't added the latest one yet, but anyway, if you look here, this is from these days when it wasn't raining.
And since I'm uploading it in real time, I have to
edit the highlights and upload them here. You can go here to see it.
Hello, Grape. Nice to meet you. I'm
doing this after dinner, but I have
some food left, so I'll finish it and
do it.
Oh, I've been exercising consistently.
Time is a bit tight these days, but I've been
consistently
[music]
[music] I
never have to wait, which is a
really good thing, but the
equipment wasn't very good. Secondly, the
equipment wasn't that bad.
There were some things that weren't there, and the originals were a bit
lacking,
but that place
had everything it needed, and it
wasn't that bad. It
was quiet, the prices were a bit cheaper, and there weren't many people, so that
was the feeling. But that place
was open six days a week and didn't open on Sundays. The
first gym also didn't open in January.
This third gym is
open 365 days a year. Oh, and the second gym is
closed on public holidays and such, so there are days I can't go here and there.
In my case, weekends are actually better because I
don't have to send packages on the weekends, so I
have a bit more free time
than weekdays. It's
a bit different from when I was in Montarang. It was
busier on weekends, but now here
in Gimcheon, I have about an hour
more free time on weekends.
Sending packages takes about an hour,
so I
go on weekends.
Mondays and such are especially
busy, so I can't go on weekdays.
That place now has a day off on the weekend,
so I was a bit disappointed, so I
looked for a place that wasn't closed on weekends, and I ended up
finding the third gym. I went there, but the
problem here was that there were too many people, and the
equipment and such were good. There were too many people. The
first one  The
gym
wasn't that crowded, but it
was still spacious outside of peak hours.
But here, even off-peak hours,
there are always a ton of people,
so I have to be
careful with the equipment. I
can't just pick and choose the exercises I want to do. The
cables are almost always full, so
there's one small one and one large one. It's impossible to do
things like cable frying on the large one all by yourself. I've never seen
anyone do that here. They
said the cables are sometimes empty. I guess it's a bit of a
business tactic.
Since there are so many people here, they only do things
like cable frying on the small one.
Anyway, there are a lot of people, which is a drawback,
but the
basics are a bit more, and the bigger one
isn't bad. The problem is that they do it on weekends,
but they
only open until 4 p.m. So today, I
thought I just had to change two tires and then balance them, but
they said they were balancing them. I couldn't understand what they were saying at all. They said the
axles
were out of alignment, so it would
be best to just replace them, but the person who said that didn't seem to
have the money to do it.  I lifted a lot
and said I
stretched as much as I could, but it's not completely stretched out, so it'll be a little like that. But I told them to just ride moderately since I was
fixing things and it
took time, so
I came in around 3:30 and
did 30 minutes until 4:00.
And actually, I did it yesterday too.
Yesterday, I did about 50 minutes, maybe 40 or
50 minutes. I
think I went in around 3:20 yesterday too.
It's good that they're open until 4:00, but if I work in the morning,
work in the morning, come home,
eat lunch, and
do other things, it takes a while to get there because
there's traffic around. It
takes about 10 or 15 minutes by car.
But they're all located
in similar neighborhoods. If you go about
10 or 15 minutes from here, you'll find a busy area
in Gimcheon. It
faces the main road, and
there's a Lotte Mart on one side, an E-Mart on the other, a
large hospital, and a road like that.
Now, these gyms are
lined up like this.
There is. These days,
when I used to work out with Taekong, I did one body part at a time. Back
then, I went every day, so I
didn't feel burdened at all even if I did one person at a time. But these days, there are
many cases where I can't go every day. I have to
work in the morning and come back. Now, on
Mondays,
Saturdays, and Sundays, I can't
send packages, so I have to send the packages that piled up again. It takes
much longer to pack the packages, and I
have to do three times as much as usual.
So, when I do things like this, it becomes
difficult to deduct time for exercise. And
if there's a landslide and the fence needs to be fixed, or if there's
a lot of bleeding and
something gets damaged and I have to do something, there are
always unexpected things that take a lot of time.
There are also many things that were expected. For example, if I run out of feed and buy feed, I
order 500km from the delivery company in one day, but it's
a bit much to use a delivery service for 500km,
so I
ask them to send it by courier. They
come by Kyungdong Express cargo.
But now, they don't often deliver to my field.
And if they
do that, the cost goes up, so I
just do
n't go that far anymore.  If you're looking for a place that's not a house,
there's a branch about five minutes away. If you ask them to send it to you through Kyungdong Express, I'll
bring my
car there,
load it,
take it to the field, and
unload it with a tractor.
Doing that takes time, and
things like that always
come up, both unexpected and expected, but time-consuming. So, I
can't work out every day, and I'm
not sure if I'll be able to go tomorrow. So,
unlike before, I've been
doing more random workouts. I've
been compressing my downtime to exercise intensely and
for short periods of time.
Before,
when I was with Daewoong, we
didn't have any cows or other animals.
Later, we
brought Muscovy, but that
was mostly the time without Muscovy. Back then,
there wasn't much to do, so I
focused on exercising.
Taewoong's job is to
exercise, so he has to work hard.
Back then, I used to work out for an hour and a half a day, every day. But
now, that's not easy, so I'm
compressing my downtime as much as possible and
focusing on multi-joint exercises.  I think I'll end up doing a bit of a mixed bag of exercises.
Rather than doing 200,000 for Part 3, I focused on chest yesterday, and
then a bit on shoulders and triceps.
Today, since I don't have much time, I'll
do back exercises. I only
did three exercises: rep
downs, long pulls, and
strong ones.
But something's
wrong. As far as I know, it's much more advantageous to
have ample rest time for the golden ratio.
Of course, I'm not
exercising with the golden ratio as the sole goal,
but since my
current
exercise schedule doesn't allow me to do it for a long time, I'm
trying to increase the intensity,
which is a bit disappointing.
Hello, Eunseong Choi and Sophie. My aunt
sent me a mini-barrier and a sweet pumpkin, so I
invited my parents.
[Music] Of
course, they won't eat the seeds, and I
know it's better to peel them and eat them. I do
n't really recommend steaming them in the
microwave. Microwave cooking is not good in the first place because it
emits a lot of electromagnetic waves. And
there are quite a few claims that microwaved food is not good either.
This is controversial now,
but
why bother using a
cooking method that's so controversial?  I don't see any reason to choose. It
might be convenient, but if you microwave
pumpkin, you'd
have to heat it for several minutes, not 30 seconds,
which would take too long, so I
think it's better to just use a pot.
How long did it take for the milk to work? It varied depending
on the
milk. Some didn't require any adaptation at all,
and even those that did, it seemed a little different for each milk. So, where you got the milk and how you ate it
seem to be important. So,
pouring it all in
seems to take longer to adapt.
Gradually increasing it little by little
seems to be faster. And
eating it with yogurt seems to help.
Rather than just drinking raw milk from the beginning, I started
eating yogurt and
starting with yogurt, or
starting with a higher proportion of yogurt.
What was it? It
was a few months ago, not recent, but it was when Taehoon was around.
Around April, there were
a lot of claims
coming out that eating mushrooms could improve cognitive function and prevent dementia, so I
became interested. So, I thought I'd
try it consistently.
I told you that I was thinking about it, but I got lazy and ended up not eating it. I think I bought it once and ate it. Meat is good, and I'm full just eating meat, but now it's not easy to put in mushrooms. But first, let me just talk about the benefits. I have
n't looked into everything. I just
looked atit roughly, but I'm
not that interested,
so I don't look into it this much. The thing that comes
up a lot from there
is the deer antler mushroom.
I think the deer antler mushroom is good for dementia prevention and cognitive function, or the pine mushroom is good for dementia prevention. I
don't remember exactly.
Anyway, the deer antler mushroom has always
been famous as a night mushroom.
I know that road mushrooms are very expensive in the West.
It's cheap in Korea, so it doesn't cost much. Honestly, it's
obviously more expensive than pine mushrooms or something, but it's
not an unaffordable price.
When I went to Ireland and
was island hopping, I
brought up the topic of gamblers. A
female
scholar who said it was good for him
appeared on a podcast and said that
eating grass is good for low blood pressure. She's a vegan.
He's not a
real person, but he's quite famous. It
's called "Reindeer Horn" in English, which is how it's called in Korean.
But the English name is much fancier, "Lion's Mane
Mushroom."
People don't
seem to pay much attention to it, but I think it's because people
in the West think of it as more sophisticated because it's called "Lion's Mane."
Of course, this doesn't apply to all Western countries, but
to English-speaking countries. Ireland
is also an English-speaking country.
When I was hopping around Ireland, the last farm I visited had a
restaurant and a farm. The owner's
sons were very interested in that kind of thing, and the
whole family was interested in health and nutrition.
He said that Reindeer Horn Mushroom was good, but it was really expensive. When I
heard that, I said, "It's really cheap in Korea." He said, "
Oh, really?" "Should
we export it?" "Should we export it?" He
said something like that.
Anyway,
back then, and even now, there's talk that
eating it
improves cognitive function and
prevents dementia.
Mushrooms, too, have seven or
so ingredients, probably to prevent dementia.
Dementia.
There are seven compounds that seem to help prevent the disease, and
two of them have been studied, and they're all about
this and that.
Most of these studies are epidemiological studies. These studies
compare groups that ate mushrooms, or groups that ate mushrooms several times a week, and groups that didn't, over a period of a dozen years. The
group that didn't eat mushrooms had a higher incidence of Alzheimer's,
or those that ate something
had a slightly lower incidence of Alzheimer's. The
exact
mechanisms aren't yet well-known, and I
know it's a poorly understood theory. It's incredibly
difficult to conduct research,
especially because there are so
many fraudsters.
Alzheimer's and dementia are
diseases that require a lot of attention and
account for a significant proportion of deaths. But
heart disease, for example,
doesn't have many people who suffer from it consistently. Usually, they just sit there and
then suddenly
have a heart attack and die.
Cerebrovascular disease,
of course, can lead to a
vegetative state after a blockage for a long time.
But vascular
diseases are usually treated in one go,
but dementia is now treated in one go.  It's
not like they died from a heart attack or something like that. It's a disease that often takes a long time for families to suffer, and it's also difficult for the patient. Because it's a disease that incurs a lot of financial and social costs, there seems to be a lot of demand for drug development. Now,
pharmaceutical companies and the FDA have been
manipulating research with their land, and on one side, they've
turned a blind eye to this.
Then, this was
exposed in a huge way, and
there was another huge scandal that all the results of research on Alzheimer's drugs or treatments over the past several decades were all garbage. So,
we still do
n't know 100% exactly why dementia occurs, and because
everything is uncertain, it's
not easy to study it accurately. It's
unlikely that it will be easy to definitively discover the exact mechanism by which eating oyster mushrooms protects against disease.
That's why we rely more on epidemiological studies.
People who regularly eat mushrooms more than a few times
have better cognitive function.
That's the
kind of research it's like.
Anyway, there
may be more high-quality studies, but
I'm not really that interested
in them.  Well, I didn't really look into it. Yes,
that's right. Anyway, I know that the mechanisms of delivery and
deer antlers
have been somewhat elucidated.
Epidemiological studies
tend to just dismiss them as mushrooms rather than specifically calling them pine mushrooms
or deer antlers. That's about it. I read an article that says that animals have heavy metals
deposited in their livers and intestines, and that if we eat animal livers and intestines, we're
consuming all of those heavy metals.
So, is it okay to not worry about it? I'm a bit concerned about seafood, as they say not to eat intestines.
Not all animals have concentrated heavy metals in their livers and intestines.
That usually applies to seafood. It's all
seafood.
And basically, you
don't have to worry about the intestines of animals at the bottom of the food chain, which don't
have many heavy metals. You know, anchovies, mackerel, herring, and sardines. You
don't have to worry about smelt, dogs, and [ __ ].
Larger animals are a bit more so.
[Music]
And now, two types of
animals, like cuttlefish and octopus, are known to have a lot of heavy metals.
But this heavy metal is what I'm talking about.
As I mentioned,
heavy metals in the ocean were
n't created and added by humans. After
the Foursquare Era,
humans didn't suddenly mine heavy metals
from the ground and add them to the ocean.
Most metalloids on the ocean floor
were formed by volcanic activity. That means they were
abundant in
the past, and animals high up in the food chain
accumulated them.
So, does that mean that
squids, who preyed on large marine animals, were traditionally exposed to heavy metal
poisoning? It's
not true.
In that sense,
we need healthy intestines, sufficient nutrients, and
plenty of nutrients to detoxify heavy metals. These
nutrients are crucial. Healthy liver
function is also crucial.
Foods that can provide these nutrients are also
seafood, which is often
considered high in heavy metals. So,
in my view, there's
no need to avoid seafood. However, the
Eskimo model relied on seafood for
survival, so they relied on it.
If the Eskimos could have eaten mammoths, they
would have. Humans
don't have a very long history of eating seafood.
For most of our time, we
lived mainly on such megafauna. Since
that wasn't possible, we
had no choice but to rely on the sea and freshwater.
That's why
meat is a more suitable diet for us.
Of course, it's good to eat seafood once in a while to
get the right amount of omega-3.
Basically,
there's no need to avoid it, but I do
n't think you need to eat more than you need in many ways. I was
eating only carnitas, but I had indigestion and had
some breathing difficulties. I
ate fruit and a small amount of vegetables, and it was
somewhat digested. Was it a potassium deficiency problem? Is it because
dietary fiber helps digestion? I
don't know how much the child ate, but I do
n't think eating a little fruit and a little vegetable would solve the potassium deficiency. Gram
for gram,
there are few vegetables that have more potassium than meat.
Of course,
even people who can easily eat 500g of salad can easily eat meat.  You
might not be able to eat 500g in one sitting, but
whatever.
Dietary fiber
can promote intestinal peristalsis, but it
doesn't aid digestion. In fact, it hinders digestion. Digestion itself doesn't help, except that it interferes with
[music] the
room. It
can, however, speed up peristalsis, allowing stool to pass
through the colon more quickly. I
don't know how you prepared the carnitas, but similarly, if your
blood sugar level spikes after eating fruit, I understand that
rapid
hyperglycemia itself promotes peristalsis. If your peristalsis is
n't working well, you
might be able to get some help. If you did
n't eat enough rice and your blood sugar level
didn't rise as much as you expected, for example, then...
Hello, Nimiral.
How about an air fryer? An
air fryer has a completely
different cooking mechanism than a microwave, so I don't
think there will be a major problem.
You can't stay here forever, so
go back home. I
think you mentioned something about being a morning person, but
I missed it. Could you briefly explain that? I
don't know which [music] Marion it was. The
steamer is too small.  Is the
oven not that great? The oven is fine.
What is the main cause of thyroid nodules?
Do you know anything about thyroid nodules? I
don't know the main cause.
Sulfate also comes to mind here. Also,
Salsa,
I
mentioned a study in the oxalate video before. I
don't remember the exact figures.
In that study,
adults
died for whatever reason. When we
did autopsies on the thyroids of the adults who died,
more than half of them. I
don't remember the exact percentage, but it
was over 50%. So, more than half of the
adults, if you do
autopsies on the thyroids of normal adults, you'll find
oxalate crystals inside. Domestically produced
crystals. Oh, and another interesting thing is that people with Hashimoto's disease don't have thyroid oxalate crystals.
Hashimoto's is a
disease where the body attacks the thyroid gland by causing autoimmune diseases.
The reason for the thyroid attack is this. Now,
this is just a guess.
Most people have oxalate crystals in their thyroids,
but people with Hashimoto's disease
don't. So,
in order to get rid of these crystals, the body attacks them and
targets only oxalate.  The sun
can't attack, so it's
attacking the thyroid gland as well, and it's causing the thyroid gland to become damaged again.
So, although the
rooftop crystals have been removed, it's
killing the thyroid gland as well. Some
people are speculating
that if the crystals are in there,
they might cause inflammation, which
could lead to nodules.
Hello, Jo Ye-na.
[Music]
Mushrooms. Why are there foods that help improve cognitive function?
Most animal foods
help with cognitive calculations.
Things like choline are also very important, and you need to
eat choline.
Choline is a single transmitter that transmits taste to the brain. It's
very important for cognitive function and attention. If you
want to eat choline, you need
liver
yolks,
seafood, and all those things that come out every day. You know, the
obvious
list. It's
good to eat them, and
creatine is also very important for brain function.
Creatine is also very high in red fish, such as sardines. If you eat 3 to
5 grams of creatine a day, you
can get up to 2 points of the maximum benefit.
But as far as I know, it's
probably not enough.  I think it was 100g, but
sardines, was it 100g
or 200g? That
's 3g of [ __ ]. That's
a lot.
But my suspicion is that it's not just sardines.
People
usually eat the intestines of sardines, so not everyone eats all the intestines of sardines
or
blue-backed fish.
I have a feeling that if there are a lot of sardines, they
would all have a lot, and herring would also have a lot,
but
that's not what they said. Anyway,
sardines
have an absurd amount of 3g of [ __ ] in 100g or 200g, which is a small amount.
Meat would have
about 1g per 500g,
right? So,
500g would have about 2g,
right? 500g would have about 2g, right? That's
probably
right. 500g is 2 grams. So if we
eat 1kg,
we
can eat about 4g.
Red meat,
right?
It was about 2g per pound.  It's
the same, so 500g would be a little over 2g.
Creatine is also very
important, and the various types of Betwell that are
included in it. When
vegans who have
n't eaten meat before
eat meat once and eat a full meal of animal spirits, their
brains suddenly
feel like they're awakened, and among these,
DHA is the biggest one. And I
think it's finally coming to light.
Both
are very important nutrients for the brain,
so if you eat a little bit of meat, you
can eat enough.
DHA is the same as seafood. It
originally had a strong savory flavor, but now that the weather is
extremelyhot, it's
not a market, but it
has a very savory smell similar to cow dung. Is it because the cow is hot?
Oh, is that my milk like that?
Actually, it's not that this arrived by courier,
but I
barely drink milk itself.
I don't know the exact taste of my milk, but I
've only had a little taste. As the
weather gets hotter,
I have one suspicion. I
can't wash it on site, so I have to kick
it and
take care of the kids, and in the meantime, I
keep the milk in the refrigerator.
But the milking machine needs to be washed.
The milking machine is just in the car during that time, and then it's
brought home and cleaned.
I wonder if that time gap is a problem, but
then it's not. One thing I
know is that it usually smells like a barn, or a manure smell,
or
especially a smell of straw. It's
literally a barn smell. The
barn smell is worse in the winter from what I've experienced. What I
mean by worse in the winter is that
the cows that are usually out
come into the barn in the winter, and that
smell comes from the smell. They come from the outside
in the pasture and come into the barn, and they
literally
live in a barn, so
I thought that's why they smell like a barn.
Yeah,
but now they probably
had a barn from the beginning, and they've always
had a barn.
Well, in the summer, they probably
eat factory-fed food.
If you go to a factory-fed farm, you know, they're
knee-deep in manure. The cows,
but if the weather is a little cold, the manure
decomposes a little slower, but
in the summer, it's more humid and
hot, so it decomposes faster.  I
guess it was used,
so now the factory farm is much cleaner when milking cows.
Since
there are standards and such all over the world, if the
bacteria count is too high during milking,
the grade will drop, and the price will not be high. So they
try to manage it in their own way. They
wash with iodine, disinfect, and
do everything they can to
produce clean milk. But
even if they reduce the bacteria count, I
wonder if they can't get rid of the smell. I
don't know,
but I don't
understand it intuitively. If you
live with a lot of poop,
won't the smell of poop get absorbed into your body? I'm not sure if that's
intuitively correct,
but I do think so.
Hello,
is mini-bun-bap safe? Is it okay to go to the hospital when you occasionally crave something dry? I
liked sweet potatoes, but I
heard they have a lot of cornstarch. You would
n't eat a ton of sweet potatoes just because you crave something dry, right? I don't think you need to worry too much about eating 100g or 200g. It's better to
eat them with other optional foods.  If not, you don't have to worry too much unless you're
eating sweet potatoes along with other foods. Sweet
potatoes go really well with milk, right? If you
eat them with foods rich in calcium, the
oxalic acid in them will react with calcium and
turn into a negative ion, so the
body will absorb
less of it.
But I
think pumpkin might be better. Wouldn't it be
better if you just remove the skin and eat it? I know that oxalic acid is
not that much, but almost none.
As for pumpkins,
between bone marrow and eggshells, which are eaten for calcium supplementation, is bone marrow more absorbable and
has better calcium quality, or are they both the
same? I
think bone marrow has a
higher absorption rate. Eggshells are calcium carbonate, so if they go straight into the stomach, they turn into calcium ions, but I don't know that the absorption rate is that high.
I know that
bones
are made of hydroxyapatite salts, so they
digest slowly when
eaten. The harmful thing about taking calcium supplements is that the
calcium concentration suddenly spikes too much, so it's hard to control that calcium
concentration.  To lower the risk, our bodies just
dump it anywhere, and
because it's dumped there,
calcium can't go to its original location, like bones, teeth, or
blood vessels, and it just accumulates everywhere, which is what
causes the problem.
Ultimately,
of course, people taking calcium supplements, or the
current culture of prescribing calcium supplements but not paying attention to vitamin AK2, are also a problem. In
any case, if you
eat bones, they're
made of hydroxyapatite, so the
calcium concentration
peaks very quickly and is known to be much less severe. It's said that
calcium spikes less, just like blood sugar spikes. It's quite
interesting. And
eating bones is
like that.
And
calcium
[music].
Eggshells are almost
pure dehydrated calcium carbonate. They
contain almost nothing else.
For example, oyster shells
contain a small amount of other minerals, very small amounts.
Butsacrum bones
contain a lot more than just calcium. About 40% of the
total weight is calcium, and the
remaining half is
protein, especially collagen protein. The
rest also contains various minerals, so they contain
a lot of phosphorus.  It's
bound by calcium phosphate.
In many
ways, bones
can be seen as having much higher nutritional value. You can eat
things that are difficult to find elsewhere with bones. They contain
powerful minerals that are crucial for bone synthesis.
In that sense,
if you have to choose between the two, it's
naturally more beneficial to eat bone.
I
think it's not just about calcium. I
heard that the
elements that occur during the protein sacrifice process and the
excessive amino acids increase the acidity of urine. Is that
okay? They say that if one's urine acidity
increases, there's a risk of kidney stones.
First of all, if you do a kidney stone carnival and the acid-
base balance is disrupted, and you
don't eat oxalic acid, you do
n't have to worry about kidney stones.
However, in reality, it's possible for the acid-base balance to be disrupted.
Theoretically, this
can be resolved to some extent by eating
bones together. If you eat bones consistently, it can be resolved to some extent. Also,
my daily lifestyle and these other things
overlap,
but my general health and these other
things are also
intertwined.  Since this is a problem, the most certain way to determine whether your urine
pH is actually dropping or
increasing is to test it yourself.
There are things like pH test sticks. If you
test it with your first urine test upon waking up, and it
goes below 5, then
rather than insisting on protecting yourself, if you're
doing carnivals, it might be helpful to
increase your intake of bye-acid by eating fruits and other things. I saw a video about
natural harvesting that suggested it might be helpful for people who haven't seen results from carnivals.
What do you
think? I
don't know why. I
think I need to hear the reason.
Also,
[music]
This is essentially a
plant-based,
physiologically active substance that
can be eaten in large quantities in places like onions.
But in this world, there are probably a lot of people who have never eaten onions in their lives, who have traditionally not eaten
onions, compared to
those who have. It's
just incomparable.
Finally, if you
look at the entire history of humanity, the number of
people who have taken QRS and not eaten onions is as large as the Earth's share of our galaxy.  Compared to the rest of humanity, they're a
really,
really
minor group, barely even three feet tall and bloodless.
When they tried to follow a diet that was thought to be universally followed by humans, like Carnivore, and failed to achieve results, they finally started eating something that had almost no history of human consumption. It's only
now that
people can eat it.
[Music]
One of the compounds in food that we can now eat is
concentrated, and in an
amount that we normally can't eat naturally, they're
extremely refined and
concentrated, and put it in a pill.
They say that if you don't take a factory-made pill supplement, you can't do anything. I really don't understand that kind of logic. It's interesting that we've
heard that the taste varies depending on the condition of the cow, but commercial
butter always tastes similar.
It could be because it's fat, but each
brand has its own unique butter flavor. If you
say it's average,
there are a lot of things to talk about when comparing milk.
Basically,
milk varies from cow to cow. This means
evaluating the taste of each individual cow individually.
But
when making butter, it's basically
all from one cow.  Butter is
n't made separately, with butter A from cow A and butter B from a
secretary.
Butter made by companies that can sell it commercially is made by mixing low-quality milk
from tens of thousands of cows,
completely uniforming the quality, and
then using that to make butter.
Naturally, any characteristics from each cow
are
inevitably diluted. And now, when we taste,
many things come into play, but
we also individually perceive the taste of fat.
This is something we didn't know before. We used to think we
perceived only five flavors, but it's
gradually been discovered that we also perceive umami, or
savory, and it seems
we now perceive the taste of fat
separately. I
don't know if it's been confirmed
yet. I think it wasn't confirmed until a few years ago. It's
also called coco-mi.
We perceive the taste of fat separately, and in the
process, we
perceive various flavors, and minerals are also
deliciously broken down. To put it simply, if you
mix Megamag with water, the
taste changes.
Depending on the mineral content, we perceive flavors very
differently.
Foods like liver have a
very strong flavor.  It feels like
there are so many minerals, especially
copper, and that's a
big deal.
Milk contains a
lot of water-soluble minerals, and
most of them are removed when it's made into butter,
so there's bound to be less variation in taste.
And if you
compare brands,
there are differences in taste.
Of course,
when you add other butters besides sweet cream butter, it's not just a
problem with the cow itself, but also the type of fermentation
bacteria used, the
fermentation environment, and
other factors, so it becomes
ambiguous.
But anyway, I
wanted to eat chocolate, so I asked the seller, and they
said that tails are a byproduct and are
used for grain purposes. I wonder
if it's okay to eat grain tails? I
wonder if there's a special way to pre-treat grains.
First of all, you're not going to eat it every
time you want.
Even if I were to try to eat only grass-fed beef, I wouldn't
eat it very often, so I don't want to
go so far as to say you shouldn't.
Of course, eating pads
would be better, or eating organic. But even if it's called "well-fed
beef," it's
not like they've been fed to cows for 30 months like Korean Hanwoo.
If it's Australian, it's
mostly grass-fed.  You have to feed them for 100 days, but I do
n't think there will be a big problem if you just eat them that much. There is
no separate pretreatment. The biggest
concern is that
[music]
graphate will replace glycine.
So,
in the process of being criticized by animals, the biggest concern is that we
will ingest graphate.
As the name suggests, glyphate is literally
taking the place of glycine in the collagen bonds, so
we
can't remove it. There is no way. There is
no way other than for it to accumulate in our bodies.
Hello, Nonami. In the
West, people say that toxins accumulate in the liver and other organs of land animals such as pigs and chickens because their
internal organs are particularly detoxifying. This is
generally not true. When Dr.
Stephanie Sneff wrote about dangerous legacies,
I have
n't verified the reference yet, but that's
what she said.
In the case of glyphate, it
tends to be more concentrated in the liver than in lean meat. It
's not a heavy metal. It
doesn't concentrate heavy metals there. The liver isn't a filter in the first place.
Heavy metals just pass through and are filtered out, and they
remain.  This is
not a detox period at all.
Yes, that's why the
concentration of heavy metals in the liver and the
concentration of neutral metals in muscle tissue are all the
same. They
say that healthy stool doesn't get on toilet paper, but
after Carnival, did healthy stool get on toilet paper? Does it
matter?
Honestly, I don't think it matters. Well, it's
hard to divide this [music] into healthy and safe. It's
just because
[music] the
state of being is
affected by many things, but
one of the biggest factors seems to be the bacterial flora from last year.
Depending on how they're structured, the
speed of peristalsis changes,
so
peristalsis is greatly slowed down, and if you
become constipated and
come out, there's a high probability that you won't need toilet paper. There's
literally not much water in the stool,
but that's not healthy either.
Constipation
doesn't require toilet paper.
And this bacterial flora from last year can of course
vary a lot depending on your eating and lifestyle habits, but
congenital
factors also have a big influence.
Of course,
there are a lot of bacteria that produce methane gas, so
peristalsis is hindered.  It won't be incapacitated
or
anything, but I think it's easy for people to have such subtle differences in
many ways. I don't think it's possible to dismiss a
healthy
disorder
or a stool condition as something that
doesn't show up on toilet paper.
[Music]
In general, is the
contrast medium really that bad? I'm not sure if the
CAC scan uses contrast medium.
Of course, if you
get a CC scan, you'll
be exposed to some amount of radiation.
Much more than an X-ray.
But I do
n't think it's something you're going to avoid right now and not get. [Music]
In any case,
since your cholesterol is very high and you
have xanthomas, I think you
have to get tested at least once.
So, whether it's contrast medium or radiation, you have to
take it at least once. I
gave my cat some Shindon Liver, but he
just smelled it and didn't eat it. Why is it that he's
never eaten it before,
or
rather, it's the first time he's ever encountered it, so he's confused about whether it's okay to eat it since he's
always eaten people,
or if it's food at all
?
When I brought my cows home, they were like, "Oh, I've never eaten it before."
At first, they barely ate grass.
Even though it was edible grass, they've only
ever
eaten TMR cases since they were born,
completely pulverized. So,
these cows have never eaten grass this long. They were
born herbivores, but the only food they've ever eaten in their lives has been
grasses and
grains that have been pulverized and mixed together, making
what would be like a human's skirt meal.
All their
lives
[music],
so that took some time.
And
honestly, even if they started eating grass through grazing, the grass
species that are common in the mountain pastures are
the ones they're used to
andeat.
But when we moved them to the next section,
there were other grasses, and they were seeing them for the first time, so
they didn't really know if they could eat this.
So, overall, it took some time for them to distinguish between green grass that's edible and
grass that's not very tasty or nutritious. Even though it's food they would have
naturally eaten during their incredibly long evolutionary history, they
seem to have trouble eating foods they've never eaten before.
Foods high in selenium  What about
selenium and [ __ ]? Are they nutrients that decrease when heated?
Selenium is a mineral,
so when you heat and the meat juices
drain, the
minerals are
lost with the juices, and if not, the
stones don't disappear when you boil them. They're not
the type that can be destroyed by heat.
As a mineral,
selenium is quite abundant even in regular meat. The
liver has more, and the
kidneys have a lot. The kidneys
have a lot,
so if you eat 100g or 200g of kidneys every day, you
could end up with too much selenium.
Similarly, Brazil nuts are the
most famous plant-based food.
Brazil nuts are also
very rich in selenium, so eating too many
can lead to selenium overdose. If you
eat them with kidneys, you
can eat a lot.
Creatine can also decrease when heated.
Sir, when eating a high-calorie meal,
eating more than 2g of bone broth would be good for excretion. It
could help reduce absorption,
but even 2g of bone broth already contains calcium.
It's a huge amount, almost 1,000 grams.
Eating that much
might not be a good idea. I do
n't want to get too hung up on calcium either.
Of course, the
tolerance for calcium from bones
seems much wider, but I still
think, for example, 20 grams might be a bit excessive.
In any case, the calcium
has to physically meet with the
calcium in the bones. In that sense, the calcium in the bones is very concentrated, so it
needs to mix and meet as much as possible in the stomach of our child.
That might not happen very well.
In that sense,
drinking milk, for example,
is a liquid form of calcium that's more dispersed. Or, you could
dissolve the shell in vinegar and then
dilute it before drinking.
If we're only concerned about the effectiveness, making it insoluble and reducing absorption in the body,
wouldn't that be more effective?
Can you eat the brain often, other than in high school?
This is a bit of a tricky question. The
brain has a psychic barrier,
so it's exposed to far more toxins than regular lean meat.  I
think it was low.
Is the brand's unique butter flavor determined by the fermentation process? The
fermentation process is important, and the grass the cows ate is
also important.
Sweet cream butters also all taste
different, right? They're butters that sweet
cream butter hasn't developed yet. Most cheap butters,
like anchor butter and
European butter,
are now sweet cream butters.
Fermentation takes a long time, and
of course, the price goes up.
Anchor butter and European butter taste
completely different. The difference is huge.
Elroy butter is the same, and even
if you don't ferment, the
taste of the watts
is different. I'll
keep that in mind. I know that
kidney stones are usually
made up of calcium oxalate.
So isn't consuming too much calcium actually
harmful? Of course, it
won't accumulate in the body, but
when oxalate combines and is excreted in a healthy way, would
n't it trigger kidney stones?
Just because
we don't eat calcium
doesn't mean we don't have calcium.
There was a time when people thought that way.
Kidney stones, like kidney stones, are all
made up of
calcium oxalate. If you investigate the composition, you'll find that more than 80% of them are calcium oxalate.
If that's the case, you
shouldn't eat calcium. If you
eat calcium, it's harmful.  The initial misconception was that oxalic acid crystals were
more likely to form stones.
However,
calcium intake
protects us from ingestion through the intestines. To expel oxalic acid
back into the intestines,
the body excretes it
through bile.
It should
n't just pass through and be reabsorbed. However,
calcium, present in our intestines, binds
with the oxalic acid excreted through bile, preventing it from forming
into a nebulized form.
This helps protect
our bodies from oxalic acid and oxalates. The
prevailing opinion is that calcium actually helps protect us from oxalic acid and oxalates.
Even if we don't eat calcium,
oxalic acid will enter our bodies and
bind to something. The most
powerful, excluding heavy metals,
binds strongly to calcium.
But just because we don't take calcium orally doesn't mean we
don't have it. There's
already a lot of calcium in our bones, and
our blood calcium
concentration needs to be maintained because it's a tight electrolyte. So,
calcium is always present in our bodies.
And the absorbed calcium
binds to the calcium that's already there anyway.
Because it helps our body excrete calcium well
and
prevents absorption, it's better to eat calcium. Eating it
helps defend against oxidative stress.
When it comes to calcium oxalate, it's not about
removing calcium,
but
reducing oxalic acid, which is a fundamental toxin. I
learned about prostate cancer through a friend and I'm studying it. My
friend
ate half and half milk and I was surprised that my
stool and brain fog disappeared around lunchtime after breakfast.
So I
don't know if it's temporary,
but thanks to you, a new world of health has opened up. The channel is currently
suspended. It's fun. Thank you. Nice to meet you.
Milk
is amazing through my friend. If
you drink it consistently with Lee Moon-chung and Brain Fog, it will
be helpful in many ways. I
don't know what kind of diet you've had,
but milk
[music] is
easy to digest and
contains almost all the nutrients you need, so they're all bioavailable.
In that sense, even
if your digestive power has been low
or you've been nutritionally deficient,
it's a food that can fill most of your needs. It
also contains glutathione,
so it's good
for antioxidants.  Because it's very effective and
very helpful,
brain fog is a type of inflammation in the brain.
Brancore comes in when there's inflammation in the brain.
But now it can help again. Is
contrast medium really bad for our body?
But if we take a CT scan without contrast medium,
if we have to
use it and we don't, the resolution will
drop. If we
don't use contrast medium in a place where it's needed, the
resolution will inevitably drop. It
's just the way the structure is.
But I'm not sure what to use. Contrast
medium isn't good. I'll have
a glass of water. I'm
having fun eating persimmons right now.
Can I eat a
lot of the inside? I don't know
how much you're eating. But even if you eat this much, it's
not a big problem. But I
don't know how much you're eating.
If you eat more than 100g or 200g every day for a long time, I
think there's a possibility of problems.
Especially if you
go outside and don't get any sunlight and
don't take vitamin D supplements,
eating a lot of liver can lead to vitamin A
deficiency and vitamin
D or other
regional vitamin deficiencies. If you
don't eat enough lean
meat and eat too much liver, the
liver also has a lot of copper due to the iron-king effect.
Iron deficiency and copper overload can occur.
These two factors
are the biggest concerns when you consume too much liver.
I saw a brief video from Incheon City Hall.
How did the report go? Can I buy it?
Milk.
First of all, we
should probably start worrying, but
at least for the time being,
the fact is that the sale of the numerical
value zone and the
purchase and sale of numerical value zones are
simply livestock product distribution. Ultimately, the Ministry of Food and Drug Safety received a report, and in any case, isn't this essentially the distribution of specialty products? They've filed a complaint. I don't think it's simple livestock product distribution. We're in the
process of clarifying the situation. Now, the
prosecutor is making a decision. I'm not sure if the prosecutor will
say, "Oh, I'm right,
so I won't indict." I hope they do that. I'll submit a written statement tomorrow. I'm
innocent. That's not true.
What I'm trying to do is, if you look at this, I'll
explain it in detail. I'll
go to the prosecutor's office and submit a written statement. I'm not
sure. I don't think the prosecutor will be the only one to give it a chance.
Flo: Actually, my expectations
aren't that high. Then I guess I'll have to
go to the regular trial judge,
but this is a real headache. It's
incredibly difficult to leave the seat like this, and I
have to attend court, so
just thinking about it is a headache. I
think it would be good if we could stall for time and hold the trial during the winter break after selling my soul,
but
considering the series of events so far and the
various things that have happened this year, I do
n't think things will work out that well.
And even
if the judge makes a ruling in the first trial, I'll have to
appeal and try several times. I think it'll be
okay this year, but I don't know what will happen next year.
Oh, but it's
a bit like that in many ways. Of
course, I was considering taking this to court, but
there are a few other regrets. First of all, I got
scammed by cattle. So,
even if I do it this year, I should
at least get a return on my investment this year,
but I've
already missed making a profit this year. It's
not 100% certain, but even if
I work my cattle until November, I'll be able to make a profit.
If you think about labor costs, it's just
a minus. If you think about not eating without considering
labor costs, it
's still a minus. Even without considering labor costs, it's a minus. Anyway, if you think about holding on until next year after work, but anyway, this kind of talk is a bit like that. Anyway, there are some regrets in many ways. It's still a bit uncertain what will happen next year.
In fact, we
were expecting a huge fight anyway.
Of course, we
thought it was bound to happen. If you
make Hwangtaekwang with Hwangtaekbae, it's delicious, so you eat a lot, but
eating too much is a bit harmful. Also, if you eat too much of this, it's
not too much. In fact, you can get enough recommended
daily calcium by eating only 2g of bone type, so it's
easy to get just a little bit, so is
there a well-organized book when it's opened? The
books closest to the liturgical diet I'm talking about are books like the
book published by Selypallowen, the director of Lesson Place by the
Western Foundation, or books written by Dr. Western Press
himself.
In fact, a more organized book is
now called
Lissom Flash rather than Dr. Western First's book.  I think the book by Foundation founder Celine
Morel would be closer,
but it's not translated yet. You can still read it in its original form.
Books like "Y Stratification" or "Diet" are
very helpful.
For books more specialized in canibo, there's "The Carnival
Code." I
haven't read it, but
there's also "The Canibo Diet" by Sean Baker. I heard
at a cafe that "Talortron"
was no joke. Do you think there's a connection between canibo and hair loss?
These days,
the rate of hair loss among Westerners is
incredibly high, at over 40%, or more than half. This is
n't just one or two people experiencing hair loss, or one or two out of ten. More than
half, if not all, of them are
bald.
Almost all of them are bald.
If you
go back at least 80 years and
look at photos of Americans taken in the mid-20th century, you'll see very few bald people.
Back then, there weren't many. If you
look at the records and photos left by observers who recorded and observed the indigenous population, you'll see
no one with hair loss.
Dr. Baldness Plus  If you look at the photos in the book,
there are a lot of people's faces. There's
not a single bald person. I
think it's true that there are people who are genetically vulnerable. But just because they are genetically
vulnerable
doesn't mean that they will develop 100% of the time.
This isn't just about hair loss, but
rather about the general situation.
Genetic vulnerability ultimately
has to be expressed, but the gene
expression is more
pronounced in some people than others, not 100% of the time. And
the gene, the
most common example of this is something like
a4a4.
In modern times, it's
called the Alzheimer's gene. If you have the A4 A4 gene mutation,
you have a much higher risk of developing Alzheimer's than the average person.
People with it often say that they
need to be careful about their risk of dementia.
But if you eat a low-carb diet and
don't have insulin resistance, like
prehistoric humans,
in that state, it doesn't
increase the risk of dementia at all, but
rather
has the ability to increase resistance to parasites.
So, it's completely unrelated.
It's beneficial. If this
gene were only bad for us, like dementia, it would
have been eliminated throughout human history.
Instead, the fact that we've carried it on until now
means that it's likely because it had a positive influence in some way.
Unless it's a one-off [music] mutation, the
gene known as the modern Alzheimer's gene
actually had nothing to do with Alzheimer's in the past.
Modern people don't eat the same diet, so it
actually
has a positive effect that helps them better withstand parasite infections. That's why
people with this mutation have survived in modern times.
Similarly,
people with genes that make hair follicles on the scalp more vulnerable to attacks by DHT are also more vulnerable.
We
don't like baldness, because it's a
more natural
state.
Animals also lose their hair as they age, becoming unsightly. Even
within animal groups,
aesthetics are
n't exclusive to humans.
Cuteness is also a human trait.
It's not a feeling that only humans have.
Baby animals are
n't cute just because they look cute to us.
That cuteness is a survival strategy.
So, when they're young, they have to
look cute. If they were to
kill me, they'd be predators,
or
other animals with evil or aggressive minds.
When they see me, they think, "Oh, I'm cute, so why not
kill me?" That's
their actual survival strategy.
Similarly, not liking the sight of hair loss and
thinking it's not a good thing isn't a unique human
trait. All animals
have it. So, if you push their fur
all the way in, dogs feel ashamed and
get depressed, and that's
not for nothing. If
there were people who had the gene that causes them to lose all their hair after they're in their 40s or 50s, they
probably left behind fewer genes. There
shouldn't have been that many, but
these days,
more than 4 out of 10 people are
bald. It doesn't make sense. A
bald person shouldn't have been
able to have that many children.
At least, they shouldn't have benefited.  You
know,
when it comes to spreading charity through children, I
think the current hair loss rate is absurd.
Just looking at modern people, if you go back to our parents'
generation, our grandfathers' generation, or our
great-grandfathers' generation, they
didn't meet that many. But these days, it's
all genetic. If it's genetic, it should all
be used for hair loss. Above that, did your grandfather,
your great-grandfather, your
great-great-grandfather suffer from hair
loss? No, it's not.
Blaming genes is a
very easy way, and
brushing it off as not your fault is very convenient and easy these days,
but it's a
different story in real life. If you
put it in food and eat it just to add flavor,
won't it be absorbed?
Quietness is almost never absorbed.
If it's not in a very strong place, it's
not absorbed.
Nutritional supplements are known for graphene.
Contrast agents probably
existed before the development of graphene. Has anything
changed these days? I'm not sure. We didn't know it was
abnormal back then, but we
eat it like meat, and are it really beneficial to the body? It's
not optimal, but it's also beneficial for
improving physical strength and treating diseases. I
heard that Jeong Sang-taek, the post-natal pediatrician, advised against eating it for the time being.  I'm not sure.
There are people who are fundamentally allergic to milk. Even if it's a tax association,
I think the biggest influence is probably the powdered milk they ate as children.
Of course, it's natural that they ate pasteurized milk and sterilized food in their growing up environment, but
babies have leaky gut because they
need it. Their
intestines aren't fully developed yet,
but they need to be
able to absorb the high-point peptide substances they receive from their mothers.
So, they're intentionally trying to organize it. In this situation, they're just pouring pasteurized milk protein into them, so I'm wondering if that's causing a tendency for allergies to dairy products.
People with severe milk protein allergies
can recover, at least for a short time,
but
there are actually many who have recovered.
Continuing to drink milk without recovery
can do more harm than good.
In a way, this is
the same with meat.
Even if you pour it in when it's not fully digested, it's not
always good.
Or, if you're bitten
by a specific tick in a foreign country, it can cause allergies.
If you have an allergic reaction to red milk, you
can't continue to eat it even if you insist on eating it. Anaphylaxis
can occur, and that's also true. While it's true that it can
be made that way,
misunderstandings are more common than those rare cases. There
are genetic differences in the ability to digest lactose. Some people can easily digest lactose
when drinking milk or in milk.
However, for
those who can't digest it fundamentally or completely, it may
not be good to eat it alone after birth.
That's why I
introduced the method of taking lactose lactase drops mixed with milk or drinking it with milk before Christmas. It's because there are individual differences that
can't be dismissed as just milk.
So, how did traditional people deal with this problem?
Mongolians
rarely eat raw milk itself. They
order it right away.
More than 80% of Mongolians have lactose intolerance,
genetically. Not everyone with that gene is
truly lactose intolerant,
but they are genetically predisposed to lactose intolerance.
Over 80% of people don't have the gene that breaks down lactose, an enzyme that persists beyond infancy.
Most people get most of their calories from milk
during the summer, which is the time of year when they
consume a huge amount of dairy products, yet most can't digest lactose.
Most of those people now
eat fermented foods and things like that.
But anyway, if you have a
genetically inherited digestive problem and drink a ton of unprocessed
yogurt and
unprocessed milk, it's
not going to be very good either.
There are some conditions.
Does canned cod liver have oil? It
usually does. Even
if you do, it'll all be written down. It'll usually say "oil" in
clothes, like "liver oil,"
or something like that.
Since it already has a lot of oil, they don't
really add any other oil. "
Hello, Lid," I
ate the video and had diarrhea.
I think I repaid it because the two-day limit was low. Two-day limit
can go bad these days. "Hello,
Ajaaja," I think our packaging has
gotten better.
Thank you. Would it be better to
keep it lukewarm for at least 30 minutes before feeding it to my baby?
How should I feed it to him?
When giving to a baby, it's best to give it at a temperature higher than room temperature.
For easy digestion, it's
best to eat it at body temperature.
It's best to give it at 36 degrees.
I also made a video about polycystic ovary syndrome.
Androgens caused by insulin resistance
are the fundamental cause.
So, the
most
urgent task is to improve insulin resistance daily. In that process, for example,
inositol is very effective. You can try taking
supplements.
Hello,
if you need help with that, is there any way I can help you?
[Music] I
wish I had a lawyer, but
I'm
not sure. It's
financially difficult to hire a lawyer, and
so on.
But I've always thought it would be
good to have something that could easily provide legal advice.
This is Joel Salatin's book, "
Everything I Want to
Do," called "Illegal."
Hey, I
have this book. I'll
show you the cover of the book I actually own.
This book.
It's on the bookshelf in the back. It's called "
Everything I Want to Do is Illegal."
It's
on the USD right now.  The farm owner, who was carrying a tank and a
gun, said, "
This
isn't an exaggeration.
Of course, as far
as I know, there hasn't been an actual case of them driving in with a tank. However, there have been
many cases of soldiers with automatic rifles driving in armored vehicles and breaking windows into the farm owner's house to raid it. This has
happened more than once or twice. In Canada and the
US, especially
with raw milk, it's common. If you were
selling raw milk in a state where it's illegal to sell raw milk, the government
would somehow find out, someone
reported it, or whatever, and then
special forces would come in with armored vehicles,
break windows, and
arrest you.
This has
happened more than once or twice.
In any case, even a good team would say that anything they want to do is
illegal,
so they say, "
Everything, everything I
want to do is
illegal." Similarly, everything I want to do is illegal.
When I was in Taebaek, I could do it illegally
without any problems. But now that I'm here, it
seems like more time has passed and there are
more people watching, so it could be
because someone with negative feelings was
just waiting for me to do it,
and
as soon as I started, they reported me. Was
it a three-year contract with the factory?
It's a three-year contract. I
don't think it can be extended. Do you think you'd ever consider writing a book about traditional Korean food? I can help you.
[Music] I've been thinking about
writing one someday,
but right now, I don't really
have all these positive feelings about writing
books. Oh, should I mention this? I don't know if I bookmarked it. Wait a minute. There's something I've been thinking about. I usually think deeply and
don't develop it to the point where I can organize it
into a single article. This person has written down what I vaguely had in mind, so I thought, "Oh, this isn't Namu's idea after all." Albolo. I don't agree with everything he says, but
he says
books are useless now. Most books are
useless and not very good.
For example, they lose value in opportunity cost. He's not saying books are useless because
there are many better methods.
Butnow,
there's Devil's Something Freddy Class, and it's
almost like most books are
useless or have no value for money.  In
fact, I've
compiled blog posts about the assembly team I've already written,
videos I've made,
and all of these things
into a book.
But on the other hand, I
wonder if it really has that much meaning anymore. When
people
think of books, they
basically think of them as something incredibly great, and they
seem to be preserving an ideal they've lost in a fantasy. I
think the value books once held has long since disappeared. What
I'm talking about now is the
value they once held.
Back in the day, when
printing technology wasn't yet adequate, it was
incredibly difficult to properly record
information, and the act of looking into other people's thoughts was
incredibly difficult and
challenging.
Creating books was incredibly valuable, and
there were no other alternatives, so it was an
inevitable act.
Consequently, the value books once held
has largely faded in modern times.
Despite this, I often think that modern people still, out of habit, praise the
status books held back then.
One of the criticisms he
raises is that, even in the astronomical community, this rarely happens. Books are
now stretched out to take up a huge amount of space. This isn't the case here,
but
here.
There are a few good points about becoming a person.
They talk about things like feeling upspace and things like that. In
the end, what they're saying is, what's
underneath it all? It's about
opportunity cost. This person's
core argument is that if
you're curious about why
people hold
political opinions and
want to explore them, you
could read a 300-page book. Or, if you
invest the same amount of time and effort,
reading only two chapters from that book, two 20-page chapters each, and then 15 other
articles,
for example, reading five Wikipedia articles,
each
35 pages each, you'll gain a broader understanding, even though you've invested the same amount of time and effort
compared to reading this one book.
This is this person's argument.
I have similar thoughts, and for
example, in my current situation,
I wrote about the liturgy
on my blog.
Then, I also
If I were to write a new book, I wouldn't just use the same examples as in the book.
Then, I would
have to use other examples.
In that case,
the groups that Dr. Press visited were
not the three I listed there, but there were
many more. They could be
Australian Aborigines, or, as in Africa,
Polynesia, the South Pacific Islands,
or North American Indians, or Peruvian Indians in South America,
or
indigenous groups from other regions.
But in fact, the stories
themselves are different in terms of examples, but the content
is the same.
In that sense, there
is an argument. Is this really
necessary?
Is it meaningful? Of course,
what other people think
is very important, so I
can't help but think about that. But at
least in my opinion,
is it worth it compared to the effort and time it takes?
I've been going on walks recently,
mostly practical books.
Richard Parkinson's
Why Cookbook, which is coming out this time, I
bought it through Kickstarter
and it will be delivered soon.
Palomersina's cookbook, and things like that,
really.  It has recipes, and
I also
bought Parkinson's Buildbook.
He runs a farm and
he's made
mobile chicken coops and
things like that. These are
mobile slaughterhouses,
not mobile slaughterhouses, but slaughterhouses anyway,
or mobile
fences, and they show you step by step how to make them,
with exactly what materials and how much to use.
They're almost
100% information-packed from beginning to end, so
there's almost no unnecessary talk. I
think books like that are really good.
In that sense, I think e-books are gaining popularity these days.
E-books are
moving away from the traditional book format and are
moving towards practical books. I think
this is a kind of trend of the times,
or something like that. To
put it briefly,
[applause]
The weather is like this. On the other hand, if you
publish a book, it
could be a source of additional income, but if you
publish in the traditional sense,
most of it goes to the publisher.
So, Richard Parkinson
sells all his books himself, to
book buyers all over the world.  They
deliver things themselves, and
there are things like that.
Now, the person who makes the entire profit from e-books also
takes all the profits. So,
in terms of profit, in the traditional
sense,
book
publishing is like that
in many ways.
Oh, there's another book that I buy a lot. It's
practical books, or
just novels. Novels are practical books in
a way.
Yes,
Hwangtaekgam is easy to make, delicious, and
cheap, so it's a must-have snack before eating. As for
snacks, beef jerky is good.
This is also good.
Even in middle and high school,
it was hard to find because of hair loss.
Hello, Mr. Pressure. Is the fascia of the fan fat,
or is it protein? Music is collagen, not
elastin. Strictly speaking, you
can think of it as collagen protein. It's a
little different, but anyway,
elastin. Elastin is a
protein, but it's not a complete protein, it's
now made up of several amino acids.  That's just the
case.
It's a shock to the formula. Orientation allergies
can be treated with a strict diet.
I'm not sure if treatment works for everything, but it
seems to be somewhat treatable for many. By taking good care of your diet, including nutrients like vitamin A and arachidonic acid that
can re-educate the immune system, and
avoiding the food you're allergic to for a while,
then gradually reintroducing it over time.
Hello, Magari.
Like before Christmas.
Can you share some tips for searching for references?
[Music]
So, basically, just because the
Western Press Foundation
published an article
doesn't mean it's correct just because the foundation said it. You
have to keep that mindset. Just
because Christmas Johnny said something like that, it can't be a reference in and of itself. Of course, as I mentioned earlier,
Christmas Sun had lactose intolerance,
but after eating it with a rock candy, I was fine. This is because he said he was
fine, but you
can't do anything with that. But
Christmas level, some kind of
academic claim, and since it was
made by that person, that in itself
becomes a reference.  It
can't be acknowledged, or it's
very difficult for me to cite it again. I
can cite it, but it's a very
weak
reference.
Expert opinion is an expert opinion claim, but an
expert claim without support
is an undeveloped
evidence base. The
highest level is, for example, a
randomized controlled trial,
double-blind, and
so on.
Or, above that, a
meta-analysis study that only includes RCTs, or
something like that.
If that's the highest level, then below that, there's
epidemiological research, and from there, the
lowest level is
expert opinion. So
expert opinion itself
can't be a reference. However, when someone
like Christmas John makes a
claim, writes, or
speaks, most people
include references along with their speech. If you
look at an article, almost
all claims have references annotated like this. You
can search for them directly by
clicking the link below.  As you can see, the
references are now organized. It's
the same for people like before Christmas.
Most of those references can be found by simply copying and pasting them on Google.
Butthese days,
there are papers like that. Most abstracts are open to the public, but you have to pay to read the full text.
In my case, I have a
friend who's still in college, so I
borrowed his university ID and
used the university library. Most of those
libraries,
like Elsevier,
demand huge amounts of money every day. They
get a lot of flak and
refuse to sign contracts.
But anyway, whether it
's a SB or something
else, most of them have
agreements that allow you to read the full text
of their papers or other things.
So, if you don't have that, it's
not easy to find the full text. You
have to
pay, and it's not cheap.
Even with just renting, it's not like you can buy a
web novel like Cookie Run or a
webtoon like Cookie on Naver
for a few hundred won.
Most of them cost tens of thousands of won or more.
That's right. It's
11 o'clock. I should be sleeping now,
but I can't. If I were to do this, I'd
always be
alone with the Souls until
dawn. At least I
could talk to the staff and stuff. But
here, I'm
really just working alone, so it's
nice to chat and broadcast like this.
Now, I should probably
go to sleep again. I'm going tomorrow morning, so I think I should go.
I'll be broadcasting again next week.
Thank you for watching.
[Music]
Please come visit again next week.